blogspot.de 2011-10-06

# MarkMonitor - Privacy Policy

MarkMonitor values your personal privacy rights. Our privacy policy is therefore adopted with a commitment to safeguarding these rights:

#### No Sharing of Information.

All information gathered is used by MarkMonitor and MarkMonitor staff only. MarkMonitor does not sell or rent user information to anyone. MarkMonitor does not share or crossreference personal information gathered through site usage with any other databases or third parties other than in two (2) exceptional cases: (1). When the site is legally compelled to do so; (2). Where disclosure is made at the request or with the written consent of the user. Therefore, unless required to do so as set forth above, we shall not respond to any inquiry from any third party unless we hold your written consent. If an inquiry is received without our having had your written consent to reply, we shall write to you requesting such consent. Our site makes no representations with respect to the creation of profiles or the use of cookies by external Web sites that have links from our site or that read and use information visible on our site.

#### Gathering of Information.

Our IP address log is used to gather broad demographic information. Our site receives feedback from members primarily through email. This information is not shared with any third party except in the two (2) exceptional cases referred to above or unless you authorize us to do so. Our site's registration form requires you, the user, to give us contact information (like your name, telephone post and email addresses). We use that information to contact you when necessary. Financial information that may be collected via secure means is used only for billing purposes. Our site uses state-of-the-art technology to keep your personal information, including your billing and account information, as secure as possible. Additionally, every MarkMonitor employee must abide by our privacy policy. Employees who violate our privacy policy are subject to disciplinary action, up to and including termination.

#### Use of Cookies.

As part of its personalized services, MarkMonitor may use cookies to store and sometimes track information about you. A cookie is a small amount of data that is sent to your browser from a Web server and stored on your computer's hard drive. All sites on MarkMonitor that are customizable require that you accept cookies. Any information obtained from the cookies will be used solely to improve our services to you. By modifying your browser preferences, you have the choice to accept all cookies, to be notified when a cookie is set, or to reject all cookies. Rejecting all cookies may limit your ability to access all areas of the MarkMonitor service.

#### Security of Service.

We have state-of-the-art security systems that are protecting your account. However, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we do our utmost to protect your information, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk. We recommend that you not divulge your password to anyone and that you do not provide access to your account to any other third party. Also remember to sign out of your account and close the browser window when you have completed your work.

#### Delete/Deactivate.

Our site gives you the option of changing your personal information. You may modify your account information at any time by clicking on the "Manage Account" link in your account page. You may also modify your account information at any time by sending an email to Email: [info@markmonitor.com](mailto:info@markmonitor.com).

#### Comments regarding Service.

We make every effort to maximize your privacy rights while you use this service. If you have any questions, concerns or comments, regarding our privacy policy or any other aspect of our service, please e-mail us at Email: [support@markmonitor.com.](mailto:support@markmonitor.com.)
